[{
    "id": "1",
    "question": "Which item does not belong in the recycling bin?",
    "answer": "Laundry Detergent Bottle",
    "others": [
        "Plastic Milk Jug",
        "Plastic Soda Bottle"
    ]
},
{ 
    "id": "2",
    "question": "Which aluminum item is not recyclable?",
    "answer": "Pots and Pans",
    "others": [
        "Soda Cans",
        "Aluminum Foil"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "3",
    "question": "When is America Recycles Day?",
    "answer": "November 15",
    "others": [
        "July 4",
        "February 14"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "4",
    "question": "What is the main natural resource to make plastic?",
    "answer": "Oil",
    "others": [
        "Coal",
        "Iron",
        "Sand"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "5",
    "question": "Is clothing recyclable?",
    "answer": "No",
    "others": [
        "Yes"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "6",
    "question": "Should you bag your recyclables?",
    "answer": "No",
    "others": [
        "Yes"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "7",
    "question": "Which of the following can you not recycle?",
    "answer": "Plastic Wrap",
    "others": [
        "Cardboard",
        "Glass Jars",
        "Cartons"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "8",
    "question": "Which of the following is important before recycling?",
    "answer": "Emptying all containers",
    "others": [
        "Taking labels off of containers",
        "Cutting up plastics"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "9",
    "question": "Is styrofoam recyclable?",
    "answer": "No",
    "others": [
        "Yes"
    ]
},
{
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Which is the most important of the recycling heirarchy?",
    "answer": "Reducing",
    "others": [
        "Reusing",
        "Recycling"
    ]
}
]